Hello I'm Sulthan Allaudeen

3.5 Years Experienced Full Stack Developer (+91)904-244-5010 | (+91)944-555-5010

https://www.sulthanallaudeen.com | http://stackoverflow.com/users/3282633 sa@sulthanallaudeen.com | allaudeen.s@gmail.com

Skills

Full Stack Developer with Expertise in Nodejs, Expressis and PHP (Laravel). I use MongoDB, MySQL to store on AWS, Heroku or Digital Ocean. Using git and bitbucket for code repo. Writes REST API across Mobile. Develops Google Script and Hybrid Application.

Experience

November 2015 - PRESENT

WeKanCode, Chennai- Full Stack Developer

- MedApp, Medical Application (MEAN Stack) http://52.57.21.92:8000
- Test My Blood, (Laravel) http://52.33.94.167/#/
- Greenhopping, Juice Ordering System (Laravel) http://www.greenhoppingapp.com

August 2014 - November 2015

Bizarre Software Solutions, Coimbatore- Backend Developer

- MTI, (Laravel)
- Adishi, (Wordpress http://www.adishi.com
- Hashtag Pizza (PHP)
- Masna Taxi (PHP)

September 2013 - August 2014

Mind Ocean Technologies, Chennai- Backend Developer

- E-Future, Learning Management System (PHP)
- Earthzu, Real Estate Portal (PHP)

Education

June 2010 - June 2013

Vel Tech Engineering College, Chennai - MCA

Interest

Programming and Stackoverflow